bigseminar.com 2015-06-16

# Privacy Policy - NameJet Domain Name Services

NameJet knows that you care about how personal information about you is used and shared and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting NameJet , you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. For questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact NameJet using our contact form.

###  What Personal Information About Users Does NameJet Gather?

Information You Give Us:
     We collect and store personal information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide us for such purposes as enhancing the experience of users in our network, responding to your requests, providing our services (e.g., domain Backorder requests, auctions, and purchases), and communicating with you about offers that may be of interest to you.
Automatic Information:
     Our Web site has features that collect information from users to assist us in creating Web sites that honor our users' preferences and serve their interests and needs.

Our Web site places cookies, which are small data files on the user's hard drive when you visit our Web site. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser; however, if you reject the placement of cookies, you may be limited in using some areas of our Web site. Some cookies are used to improve your user experience by making login to our Web site easier, such as by remembering usernames and passwords. Cookies can also enable us to monitor users' movements through our Web site so that we may target user interests to enhance their experience at our Web site. We may also collect click stream data such as the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) and assign unique identifiers to our users for the purpose of tracking user behaviors. Information obtained with these technologies may be associated with the personal information you have provided us. Besides using the information as described above, NameJet may utilize cookies to control operations such as the flow of the ordering processes related to your online transactions.

We, or our third-party advertising partners, may also place cookies to provide advertisements about goods or services that may be of interest to you. Since our advertisers and other third parties whose products or services are promoted on our Web site may also use cookies or other technology, we advise you to check the advertisers' privacy policies for information about their privacy practices.

We may also gather general information such as the date, time, browser type, operating system, platform, navigation history, and IP address of all users to our site(s). We use this information for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, and system administration, and to gather broad demographic information about our users. We may also associate this general information with your personal information. By visiting our site, you affirmatively consent to our collection, use, and distribution of your general and personal information and other related data to our partners and advertisers. If you do not want us to share information about you with our partners or advertisers, you may opt-out of receiving information by doing the following:

  1. Login to "My Account".
  2. Click on "Edit my Account Settings".
  3. Select the "My Preferences" tab.
  4. Choose your email settings under "Email Preferences"
  5. Select the option not to receive advertisements.

###  Does NameJet Share the Information It Receives?

Yes, we do share information with at least the entities listed below:

WHOIS:
     We are required by the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN"), the organization that assumes responsibility for domain name allocation, to collect information about you during the domain name registration process. This information includes your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number. ICANN then requires all registrars to make your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number, as well as the creation and expiration dates of your domain name registration and the name server information associated with your domain name, to the public via an interactive Web page and a "port 43" WHOIS service. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy we will refer to this information as your "WHOIS Information." Please note that we may not be able to control how members of the public may use the WHOIS Information.
Advertisers:
     We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers.
Partners:
     We partner with other third party providers of specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, e-mail addresses, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.
Agents:
     We engage other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments, providing marketing assistance, providing customer services, sending postal mail and email to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These persons have access to user information needed to perform their functions for the benefit of the user. These companies may, or may not, retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information that you provide to NameJet for any secondary purposes.
Service Providers:
     We engage other companies and individuals to perform enhanced services on our behalf. For example, we my engage another service provider to provide free electronic mail services to our domain name registrants. Many of our service providers have access to personal information needed to perform these kinds of services.
Business Transfer:
     As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, if NameJet , or substantially all of its assets, were ever to be acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Compliance:
     We release account and other personal information when we believe release is required to comply with federal or state law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of NameJet , our users, or others. This includes at least exchanging information with other companies, organizations and members of law enforcement to protect against fraud or other criminal activity.

###  How Secure Is Information About Me?

The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, disclosure, or destruction of that information. We protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input and the information we may send to our agents. NameJet has gone to great lengths to ensure your information is securely obtained. For example, we encrypt your credit card number before it is stored in our database. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

###  What Information Can I Access?

NameJet gives you access to certain information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. To view or change this information, log-in to your account. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

###  Links

Sites provided by NameJet contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

###  Children

NameJet does not sell services for purchase by children under the age of 18. If you are under 18, you may use our services only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

###  Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit NameJet 's Web site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the Commonwealth of Virginia. If you have any concern about privacy at NameJet , please send us your concern using our contact form, and we will address it. Our business changes constantly. This Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our policy and conditions but you should check this Privacy Policy posted on our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

If you feel that NameJet , or any of its agents, representatives, or employees are violating this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail using the contact form or by telephone at 1-425-974-4687.
